hey everyone thanks for listening to the
grow your life podcast my name is
jeremiah krakowski and on this podcast i
talk about ways for you to grow in your
life and your business to make more
money live the life of your dreams and
reach your goals faster if you're a
coach if you're a trainer and you want
to know how do i make more money like my
client joshua he just made 50 000 this
past week in his business like my client
rick who did over a million dollars this
month
i want to show you as a coach or trainer
how you can do the same
and it's not rocket science even if you
just want to make an extra two thousand
five thousand dollars a month this works
these strategies work at the beginning
and all the way to the top but you're
not going to get there until you apply
them and this is the biggest thing that
i see that stops a lot of entrepreneurs
is
how they make their decisions
how they
live their life how they choose to go
about their
day and
and i'm gonna i'm gonna keep this a
hundred with you
i'm gonna say some stuff that might come
across harsh today
so let's put on our big girl and big boy
pants
and realize that
this is based off of
thousands of people that i've worked
with
and the biggest things that separate the
ones that fail from those that succeed
and if you can get these things there's
not a whole lot of them
you will start to see
more results in your business
number one thing that i see
that business owners when they get
started that they do
is they complain
in the beginning i don't have enough
time my kids my family my
responsibilities my stuff at church or i
don't have enough
money i'm not making enough money to be
able to
get these systems or sign up for this
coaching program or or do that or my
life is in too much chaos too much
disarray for me to do that now here's
the thing at the end of the day you get
to choose how much money you make yeah
you do and i need you to believe that
i need you to realize that you are 100
in control of how much money you make
you're not a victim
okay
if you want to increase the money you
make you can sell stuff you can go do
some other things temporarily to make
money
you're not a victim
if you think that you're a victim
you're always going to be a victim to
how much money you have and the amount
of money that you have is going to be
the controlling system in your life
the
number in your bank account is going to
be
your master and commander
until you decide to have control over
how much is in that bank account
it's a decision and it starts by you
believing that you're worth making the
kind of money that you want to make
that's a good thing for you to make that
much money
and that it's time for you to start
believing that you can
okay
then the other thing is is that
we got to have boundaries priorities
time management i don't have enough time
it's usually because we're saying yes
i'll do that i'm going to do that i have
to do that to too many things that we
don't really need to do
because we've always done them and
because not doing them produces some
kind of guilt in our lives
okay
and so learning to say no to stuff even
if it's painful even if you feel guilty
even if other people rip into you and
tell you that you're a bad person for
not doing them
you're going to have to choose
what you're going to do and then start
building your business with that time
especially if your funds are low
especially
until you can start to hire some people
and there's resources like online jobs
that ph that you can use to hire people
to help you build your business
and that last one all my life is too
chaotic i'm telling you the more money
you make your life is going to get more
chaotic
don't think that
it's going to suddenly get calm
and that once it's calm you can go up
the higher you go the less calm it is
so you got to learn to operate in the
chaos instead of waiting until it's all
in order
it's a fairy tale to think that
sitting around waiting to have more
money to have more time and to have more
order and waiting until you finally have
this
going on
is going to help you build your business
because that day isn't going to come
until you choose that those three things
time money and chaos
are not your controllers in life that
they are not your boss
that the amount of time you have is not
the dictating factor of your ability to
make money
at the amount of money you have is not
the dictating factor of you being able
to build your business and make money
that the less or more order or chaos
there is in your life is not the
dictating factor of you being able to
make more money
and that you start to build with what
you got even when it's uncomfortable
even when you feel
like man i wish it it should be this way
it's all supposed to be this way yeah
great awesome it is but it's not
so you're gonna wait another five to ten
years till it is
unfortunately that's what most of you
are going to listen to this podcast
you're going to do
how do i know that i know that from the
data of working with thousands of people
because that is literally
what most people do is they will hear
exactly what i'm saying
in one ear out the other ignore it and
for some reason they have the conviction
that christians do about jesus christ
dying on the cross and rising from the
dead that it's not these things and that
that someday magical fairy dust is gonna
fall down in their life and they're
gonna have perfect order and enough
money
and enough time by doing nothing
by waiting and then finally doing when
it when it feels good that they're going
to finally step out of the boat and take
a leap of faith when the waters are calm
i'm sorry you got to step out of the
boat when the waters are rough it's the
only way that you can succeed
and so getting this mindset down
is important
figuring out
why is this controlling you what beliefs
have come in that have told you
that you can't prioritize things or
you're a bad person
that you have to wait until you have a
certain amount of money
or you're
a bad steward of your finances
that things need to be perfect in an
order
or you're going to be unsafe and things
aren't going to work out whatever taught
you those lies
whoever taught you that maybe it was
your parents
your grandparents your teachers
a mentor sometime
whoever taught you that i'm telling you
i've been around amazing mentors that
have made millions of dollars and they
all say the same thing
and every single broke person i meet you
want wanna know what they say well
jeremiah you're you're just generalizing
it's it's not always that way for
everybody honestly a lot of people they
just need to wait they just need to wait
great stay broke
with that mindset
because literally that mindset will keep
you broke until you change it
until you decide
that in the midst of hell going on in
your life that you're going to do stuff
stop waiting for perfection to come
stop waiting for it all to be sunshine
and rainbows to start doing what you
need to do
and start building your business
with the resources with the time with
the energy with the knowledge that you
have right now instead of being afraid
of messing up making mistakes or it not
working out instead of letting the fear
of things not going how you want and
being such a freaking control freak
literally that's what it is it's being
such a control freak over everything in
your life
that you won't do anything until you got
total absolute power control
it's ridiculous
and yet this is what most entrepreneurs
in the beginning do and operate deep
inside of them
they won't do
anything
until it's all perfect
until they got the perfect number in
their bank account now i can finally do
it that number's never gonna freaking
come my friends
until you start doing something until
you start getting into an environment to
learn and to grow and to start building
your business instead of letting the
lack of knowledge lack of skill lack of
time lack of money control and dictate
the level of success that you can have
in life
you have the power to not let those
things
be the be the god in your life literally
they become idols
in our lives
that we bow down and worship
it's like this like like this idol that
we're like yes lack of time you are my
master lack of time give me more time
and i will finally do what i should
bowing down to an idol lack of money
lack of money you shall have total
control over my life lack of money once
i have enough money thou shalt give me
blessings seriously that's what it is
it's exactly what it is
it's idolatry
worshipping
your situation
and it's not going to get you anywhere
it's not
oh god of perfect order come
give me all my blessings
god of no chaos come
this is literally what people are doing
hoping
that one day
in fairy tale disneyland magic dust
mickey mouse world
things will change without doing
anything
or the things they're doing are are not
changing
they're not growing their business
because for some reason they've
convinced themselves i have to do these
things first
you don't have to do anything first
you have to do something
get it out of your head that there's a
perfect order that things need to go in
get it out of your head that if you
don't do things perfectly you're gonna
fail and that failure is the worst thing
in the world in fact
making mistakes and failure is the best
thing that you can do if you're not
failing on a regular basis you are
literally not doing enough
you're not
if you're not constantly having failure
after failure after failure after
failure you are not doing enough and you
are the only person in control of that
because you're too afraid
of not being in control
too afraid of not looking perfect to
people
too afraid of appearing
less than and and you've convinced
yourself that you're not good enough
right now
to do it
you have everything inside of you right
now to
that start succe in yourself the level
of self-esteem that you have in your
life
is what's going to change things and i
don't care who told you that you were
worthless
stop replaying this tape and the memory
of what other people have told you in
your life that you're not good enough
that you need to be a certain way in
order to start building your business
the only thing you need to do is do
something
and and it ha and the something that you
should do
should not have anything to do with
being a being better getting better
becoming more good enough you're already
good enough how you are right now today
even if you don't feel like it
and so start taking action
even when you feel
that imposter syndrome instead of
self-sabotaging
and waiting until all the little pieces
come together perfect for you
if you're in my client growth
accelerator you can learn step by step
by going through the courses and hopping
on the training calls the group coaching
calls what you need to do
i don't have time to do that it's your
choice
what you choose to do
when you choose to do it
are you going to keep letting your
excuses be god in your life and dictate
everything about what you can and can't
do
are you going to get up and actually
start to do something
the choice is yours
it makes me exhausted and saddened
to see people with so much potential
say well once i get my money in order
then i'll start doing something and
they've been saying the same thing for
seven years
i know i know a guy he's on his he's on
his tenth year of the same stinking
excuse
and then i have a client who in less
than six months is making over 100k a
month
by doing something
when he started six months ago it wasn't
working at 100k a month it only did 5k
then 15. then 30.
have a client doing a million a month it
started by doing something and taking
action imperfectly and not being afraid
of
needing to be in a certain place needing
to be good enough needing to have your
life in order a certain way and in total
control for you to feel safe inside that
lack of safety usually comes from trauma
usually comes from somewhere in your
past you were taught that
if things aren't a certain way
bad stuff happens
and you're living your life based off of
that belief
letting the situation of your past
run
you you have to reprogram your brain
i had to work with a therapist to do
this
i had to get some professional help to
do this
some people need to get help
to do this instead of us living on an
island trying to be a lone wolf oh
here's the here's here's
fourth one one of the worst things
entrepreneurs they don't ask for help
they think that they need to do it all
on their own or it's not good enough
that if they ask for help they're
somehow
worth less as a person and that their
results are worth less by getting help
because
for whatever reason
usually high school
teenage years
that if you needed help with something
you were you were bullied
or told that you were not as good enough
of a person
and made to feel guilty for the fact
that you needed help
and then they're business owners that
literally they have opportunities
they literally buy packages of
one-on-one coaching with me and don't
schedule calls
and yet have access to
being able to get the help they need and
refuse to because of their own pride and
ego
refuse to and and when i ask they say oh
i'm
getting my stuff in order
get my stuff going on i'm sorry but like
you've been saying the same thing
for years
when is it gonna happen
it's eventually gonna happen no it's not
so you gotta get out of the boat do
what's uncomfortable get started start
doing it even before you feel ready to
and just be willing to make a mess and
have fun along the way
instead of attaching so much
putting
it on a pedestal
and i need the oh
the perfect life before i can get
started like it's ridiculous it is
start doing
something
ask for help ask for guidance instead of
being so prideful that you gotta keep it
into yourself
that you gotta
never get anybody to help you because
for some reason you feel like you're
less
less of a human being for needing help
whoever lied to you and taught you that
i'm sorry
that they completely effed you up for
the rest of your life
yeah i said that
i said the f word
they completely screwed you up for the
rest of your life
usually it's people that love us too
and if they knew the damage that they're
doing and how do i know that they're
doing damage
because i've seen it with thousands of
people
it's the same thing every time
and yet there's people right now
listening to this podcast
who are going to get mad at me for what
i'm saying for what i've just said
and
one day they'll get it
for those that finally do get it
they're going to start to see some
results
and that's what i'm excited about i care
so much to help people get results and
to not patty cake around i don't want
people paying me money in my coaching
program just to be in a kumbaya club
i want people that are going to be
taking action
even if it's not perfect
be willing to fail be willing to make
mistakes
be willing to do something just to see
what happens
be willing to experiment be willing to
test
instead of trying to wait until this
almighty perfect day where they finally
have it all figured out and then they
can do something
the day is never going to come
it's time
for you
to start
with what you have in front of you
give it your best shot stop complaining
stop comparing yourself to other people
and thinking that you have to be where
they're at to get started they started
where you're at every single one of them
did
the only difference is they didn't sit
around and wait till they were where
they are to start they started with what
they had
every time
and that's what produces results my
friends
take action now
stop waiting
if you're ready to jump into a community
of people that are taking action and to
stop making excuses that i'd love to
have you in the client growth
accelerator
i'd love to help you make
twenty thousand a month fifty thousand a
hundred thousand dollars a month in the
program or even if you just wanna make
your first two to five thousand a month
how would that change your life i'd love
to help you do that
jump in over jeremiahkowski.com
forward slash accelerator
and let's start making you money and
help you get rich
talk soon have a good one